ukulele-tabs.com 2019-10-22

# Privacy Policy | Ukulele Tabs

### Last modified: May 5, 2018

As the operators of this website, we take the protection of your data very seriously. We keep your personal information confidential in accordance with all applicable legal provisions and this data protection statement.  
You can exercise your right to access and make changes to your personal information by reaching out to us via our contact form. You can adjust your cookie settings to allow website visit statistics and targeted advertising, tailored to your personal interests. These settings can be accessed from the menu located on left site of every page on the site. 

In general, our site is fully accessible without providing any personal data. In the event that our site does request personal information (such as your name, postal or e-mail addresses, etc.), we ensure that providing such information is voluntary, whenever possible. Moreover, this data is never given to third parties without your express consent. The following statement provides an overview of the types of data we collect, how this data is used and transmitted, what security measures we take to ensure that your data is protected and how you can learn more about the information you’ve transmitted to us. 

Nevertheless, we must advise that any data transmitted over the internet (e-mail communications, for example) may be vulnerable to security threats. Seamless data protection against third party intruders is not possible. 

#### Collection and Retention of Personal Information

In general, our site can be used without communicating your personal data. We do, however, record your IP address and information regarding the browser used to access our site. All other personal information (such as your name, postal and e-mail addresses, etc.) is communicated to us on a strictly voluntary basis, as part of an application or registration process, for example. We never share your personal data with third parties. Personal information relating to our members cannot be stored beyond the length of their membership.  
However, all data which establishes proof of ownership, proof of a contract or which must be kept in compliance with a legal obligation may be subject to an intermediate archiving policy. Such information shall only be retained for the minimum period required by law, in accordance with all applicable provisions for the nature of the data in question. 

#### Cookie Use and Web Analysis Tools Privacy Policy

"Cookies" are small pieces of data which store information about you on your computer when you visit our website. Cookies help us identify how many users we have and how frequently these users visit our website. As a result, we are then able to design personalized offers in a way that is both practical and efficient. 

We use [Google Analytics](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage), a web-based analysis service provided by Google Inc. Google Analytics uses "cookies", text files that are stored on your computer and that allow your site usage to be analyzed. The information collected by these Cookies regarding your site usage is transmitted to a server where it is stored. This information is used to evaluate how the site is used, to generate reports regarding the site’s audience and activity and to provide other information regarding site and internet usage for market studies aimed at meeting user needs and enhancing user experience. The IP address provided to Google Analytics by your internet browser is not aggregated with other Google data. These IP addresses are rendered anonymous, thus ensuring that identification is impossible (IP Masking). 

Our site is also usable without Cookies. In your internet browser’s settings, you can completely disable cookies, limit cookies to only certain website or request that your browser inform you any time a cookie is sent. However, please note that if you choose this option, you should expect a limited representation of our site and limited user guidance. 

#### Exclusive Member Areas

To access certain features of the site, you’ll need to create a member account. When creating your account, we record your IP address, e-mail address, date of birth, gender and country of residence. Other information may be communicated to us on a voluntary basis (first and last name, city, etc.). Each time you connect to our site, we record your IP address for legal purposes, in accordance with our Terms of Use. This data is not communicated to any third parties.  
The data you share in the member area can be erased or modified at any time within the member area. 

#### Newsletter Data/Partner Offers

If you would like to receive a newsletter or any of our partner offers, you must first create a member account. We will require your e-mail address, as well as information allowing us to verify that you are the rightful owner of the provided address. In addition, you must provide express consent to receive the aforementioned newsletter(s) and/or partner offers. We use this information exclusively to send you the information you have requested, and it is not communicated to any third parties. 

#### Contact Form

When you make a request using our contact form, the information you provide on said form, as well as your IP address, will be retained by us so that we may resolve the matter in question and respond to any additional questions which may arise. We will not transmit this data without your express and prior consent. 

#### YouTube Privacy Policy

Our websites offer features that rely on YouTube, a service operated by Google. The provider is YouTube LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, United States of America. Should you visit a page with a YouTube player, a direct link to YouTube servers will be established. As a result, the YouTube server will be informed of the websites you have visited. 

When you are signed in to your YouTube account, you allow YouTube to add your browsing habits directly to your YouTube profile. You can prevent this by simply logging out of your YouTube account. You can find further information regarding how user data is handled in YouTube’s Privacy Policy [here](https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy). 

#### Privacy Policy for Other Plug-Ins and Social Networks

Our site offers direct links to servers for various social networks and plug-ins. As a result, social network servers will be informed that you have visited our site. We must emphasize that as a web page provider, we have no knowledge of what content is transmitted, nor how this content is used by the various social networks in question. 

When you are signed in to your social networking accounts, you allow these networks to add your browsing habits directly to your profile. You can prevent this by simply logging out of your accounts. 

You can find further information regarding how personal information is handled in the privacy policies of each social networks. This information can be found using the following links to their respective pages: [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php), [Twitter](http://twitter.com/privacy), [Google +1](https://developers.google.com/+/web/buttons-policy), [Pinterest](https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy), etc. 

#### Information, Removal, Modification

At all times, you have the right to freely access any personal data belonging to you which has been stored, to know who has had access to the aforementioned data and to know why it was initially been recorded, as well as to modify, block or remove this information. The data you share in the member area can be erased or modified at any time within the member area. For all other questions relating to your personal information, please contact us at the address indicated in our legal data. 

#### Privacy Policy Validity

This Data Protection Statement is currently valid and originally dated July 19, 2017. Updated May 5, 2018
